I want to believe your hearts are blessed.
Rise up for prayer.
I will start my prayer by praying for those who are still in bondage.
To all hearts that are in bondage - be free, in the name of Jesus!
Bondage of unforgiveness - be free, in the name of Jesus!
Bondage of bitterness, anger, envy, jealousy - be free, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers at home, viewers all over the world,
to all hearts that are in bondage - bondage of unforgiveness, envy, jealousy, anger -
be free, in the name of Jesus!
Yes, we can move.
I want to believe you are free.
Say, "Thank You, Jesus, for freeing my heart to follow You".
Thank You, Jesus, for freeing my heart to follow You.
"Thank You, Jesus!" - you must mean it!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Right now, prepare a way for your deliverance and open your lips.
Whatever hinders your deliverance - give way!
Open your lips.
Whatever hinders my deliverance - begin to give way right now!
Begin to give way!
Whatever hinders my healing - begin to give way!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Whatever hinders my deliverance - give way, in the name of Jesus!
It could be doubt, unbelief!
Whatever hinders your deliverance - right now, begin to give way!
Viewers all over the world, open your lips.
Whatever hinders your deliverance - right now, begin to give way, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to give way, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name!
[Amen!]
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Holy Spirit, rain on us Your power of deliverance!
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Holy Spirit, rain on us Your power of deliverance!
Begin to rain on us!
Holy Spirit!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Holy Spirit, rain on us Your power of deliverance!
Rain on us, oh Holy Spirit!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Rain on me!
Open your lips! Say, "Rain on me Your power of deliverance, Holy Spirit!"
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Watch your screen.
Holy Spirit, rain on us Your power of deliverance!
Holy Spirit, rain on me Your power of deliverance!
Your power of deliverance - rain on me!
Power!
Glory!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Holy Spirit, You are welcome! Rain on us!
Rain on them!
Rain on us!
Rain on me, Your power of deliverance!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Continue to watch your screen
and see what the power of the Holy Spirit is doing right now.
The poison in the life of the people has been flushed out.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
You can see them vomiting out poisonous substances from their system.
Come down, in the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Every disease in your blood, bones, tendons - I command them out!
I say out!
In your blood - out!
In your tendons - out!
In your bones - out!
In your kidney - out!
In your liver - out!
Say out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Continue to watch your screen and see different substances.
Come on!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Say, I command you, you disease!
You affliction in my blood - out!
Say out!
Out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I command that disease, that sickness - out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Viewers all over the world,
I say to you, you disease - power!
Out!
In your blood, kidneys, liver - I say out, in the name of Jesus!
Command it out!
I say, command it out!
Tell that disease, that sickness - say out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Come on!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Watch your screen.
You are still witnessing the evidence of the power in the name and blood of Jesus Christ.
People are vomiting and those who possess contrary spirits are being exposed right now.
Holy Spirit, begin to rain on us!
Power of healing, rain on us!
In the name of Jesus!
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Watch your screen and see blood and other substances in that vomit
to show that it is the trouble in the life of the people - affliction, sickness disease -
that they are vomiting out right now.
In the name of Jesus!
I say, that disease - leave my people!
I say, leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
Come out!
There is rain.
Power of healing - rain on you!
I say, rain on you!
Power of healing, in the name of Jesus - rain on me!
Rain on me - power of healing, in the name of Jesus!
Rain on my blood, kidneys, liver, bones, organs - power of healing!
Prayer!
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Come down!
You affliction, no hiding place!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
She belongs to me!
Come on!
I command thee, you affliction in the bones, kidneys, liver - out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Where can we go from His presence?
Rain - power of healing!
In the name of Jesus!
Prayer!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Right now, begin to seal your blessing with the blood of Jesus!
I seal my healing with the blood of Jesus!
I seal my deliverance with the blood of Jesus!
Open your lips and seal it!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Begin to cover your partner with the blood of Jesus,
your business with the blood of Jesus,
your finances with the blood of Jesus.
I cover you with the blood of Jesus!
Begin to cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
Cover your business with the blood of Jesus.
Cover your finances with the blood of Jesus.
Cover your marriage with the blood of Jesus.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I can't hear your amen!
[Amen!]
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Your heart, agree you are blessed.
My heart, agree I am healed.
When your heart agrees you are healed, you are healed.
You are healed indeed!
Give thanks to God.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
The pain of cancer is gone!
The pain of cancer of blood, cancer of kidney is gone!
[Amen!]
Check yourself. That pain, that affliction is no longer there!
Check yourself and say, "Thank You, Jesus!".
Hallelujah.
Give thanks to Him.
Right now, your country, your nation.
Have your flag - whatever you have as a contact.
Open your lips.
Commit your nation to God Almighty.
Commit your nation.
God's intervention.
Your nation - open your lips.
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Begin to cover your nation with the blood of Jesus.
Cover your country with the blood of Jesus.
Open your lips. Cover your nation.
Cover your country, your leader with the blood of Jesus.
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Give thanks to God.
God is in control.
God is in charge.
Tell yourself, "God is in charge; God is in control".
Give thanks to Him.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Hallelujah. Give thanks to Him.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
[Amen!]
Right now, if you are just coming to the Lord Jesus and you have known Him for the first time,
let us pray for you right now,
and for those who are here to rededicate themselves.
Lord Jesus, come into my heart, wash me with Your precious blood.
Lord Jesus, make me a channel - Your channel of shining light.
Make me Your channel - Your channel of love.
Lord Jesus, make me Your channel - Your channel of pardon, where there is injury.
Lord Jesus, make me Your channel - Your channel of forgiveness, where there is sin.
Lord Jesus, I thank You, Lord, for dying in my place.
Thank You for my salvation!
Right now, rejoice in your salvation!
You can be bold to say, "I'm a channel of love where there is hatred.
I'm a channel of God, channel of love, where there is hatred.
I'm a channel of light where there is darkness.
I'm a channel - a channel of forgiveness where there is sin.
I'm a channel - a channel of obedience where there is disobedience.
I'm a channel of pardon where there is injury".
Rejoice!
TT: Mel Flowers 18/07/2018
RV ROBERT BEGIER 21/07/2018